Ms. Christmas Comes to Town is a tv movie, drama,
romance film directed by Jason Bourque.
Christmas, a shopping channel host, receives a terminal diagnosis, she
heads on a multi-city excursion to spread Christmas cheer.
Amanda, played by Erica Durance.
Travis, played by Brennan Elliott.
Gayle, played by Barbara Niven.
Murray, played by Chris Gauthier.
James, played by Mark Brandon.
Elizabeth, played by Judith Maxie.
That Christmas is a 2024 animated Christmas fantasy comedy film directed by Simon Otto
(in his directorial debut) and written by Richard Curtis and Peter Souter.
Produced by Locksmith Animation, it follows entwined storylines based on short stories from
That Christmas and Other Stories by Curtis and illustrator Rebecca Cobb.
The voice cast features Brian Cox, Fiona Shaw, Jodie Whittaker and Bill Nighy.
That Christmas premiered at the BFI London Film Festival on 19
October 2024, and was released on Netflix on 4 December.
The film received a mixed response from critics.
The film explores themes of holiday, christmas, candid.
The tone is emotional.